MYRIAM CISTERÉ GARCIA

Architect/Project Manager

Personal Details

Email: myriamcistere@hotmail.com
Nationality: Spanish
Skype: myriamcistere
Marital Status: Single

Languages Spoken: English, Spanish and Catalan **Driving License:** Spain Driver's License B1

 I have 10 years of experience in Construction, Design Execution, Constructability and Project Management.

For the last few years I have fully engaged with site activities, Supporting and assisting field Engineers, Managing site changes, monitoring progress and the execution of works and building small projects on my own. At all times I try to ensure the design meets the scope of the contract, schedule and quality requirements, and the work is performed within budget.

Work Experience

10/2013 – 11/2013 Project Manager - Jimaran Construction Company. Tarragona. Spain

- Previous Studies, Tenders, Quotations and Feasibility of various projects.

01/2012 – 05/2012 Site Project Manager - TCSA Construction Group. Tarragona. Spain

 Evaluate Quotations, Sending inquiries to all major subcontractors and suppliers, Prepare the comparative statements of subcontractors/ suppliers.

 Coordination with internal departments like projects, procurements, production and external parties.

Building the Changing Rooms in Ascó Nuclear Plant - ANAV.

07/2010 – 01/2011 Site Project Manager - PROINTEC Engineering Group. Tarragona. Spain

 Development of Urbanization and Changing Rooms Project in Ascó Nuclear Plant - ANAV.

Development of Industrial buildings for nuclear plants.

- Coordination & Construction of Civil Works.

05/2009 – 02/2010 Project Manager - Property Developer TR CORPORATION. Barcelona. Spain

- Coordination & Development of Housing Projects.

09/2006 – 05/2009 **Project Coordinator** - Santi Soto Architecture Studio

(Professor School of Architecture of the Vallès, UPC). Barcelona. Spain

- Development of Multi-family housing construction projects and Public facilities. Promotions: GISA, INCASOL, PROMUSA and others.

Coordination at all stages of project teams Installations and Structures,
 Management, College of Architects, Developers, Contractors, etc.

- Managing, planning and organization of the Studio.

07/2005 – 09/2006 Assistant Project Manager - Architecture & Urbanism Busquets Studio, SL

Joan Busquets (Martin Bucksbaum Professor of the Graduate School of Design at Harvard University since 2002 Professor of Urbanism and Architecture School of Architecture of Barcelona, UPC since 1979) working on projects such as construction and performing urban planning and preliminary competitions. Barcelona. Spain

02/2004 - 07/2005	Assistant Project Officer - Architecture & Urbanism Busquets Studio.
07/2002 - 09/2002	Assistant Project Officer - Gonzalo Gracia Architecture Studio. Tarragona.
07/2000 - 09/2000	Assistant Project Manager - GUINOVART & OSHA Construction. Tarragona.

Freelance Works

2005 - 2014 Proposed **renovation and extension** of a detached house. Finished building.

Housing **Rehabilitation** Project. Finished building. Housing **Interior Project Reform**. Finished building.

Project building **2 houses**. Finished building. **Commercial building** Project. Finished building.

Proposed **renovation and extension** of a house between dividing walls.

Finished building.

Project detached house between dividing walls. Finished building.

Academic Qualifications

2011 – 2012 MASTER'S DEGREE in Project Management

Business Engineering School La Salle, Ramon Llull University, Spain.

1998 – 2005 BACHELOR'S DEGREE in Architecture

Barcelona School of Architecture, Polytechnic University of Catalonia,

Spain.

Languages skills

English First Certificate English (FCE) – Level B2 (2013) – University of Cambridge.

Spanish and Catalan Mother tongue.

Additional Qualifications

2013	"Energetic certification of existing buildings: methodologies and
	normative tools (CE3, CE3X)" Sert School, College of Architects of Catalonia
	(COAC).
2010	"Coordination of Safety and Health in the Construction Works" Sert
	School, College of Architects of Catalonia (COAC).
	"Lighting Exterior lighting designs. Light Pollution and Energy Efficiency",
	UPC School.
2008	"Basic criteria for installations in Housing buildings" Sert School.
2007	"Simple calculations for the proposed structures and foundations" Sert
	School, (COAC).
2006	"Real Estate Valuations" Sert School, (COAC).

Computer Skills

MS Project Advanced Level.

Autocad v.2010 Advanced Level. Course 60 hours **Autocad** in Carban Academy (1999).

MicroStation User Level.

Adobe Photoshop Infographic Architectural Course at the School of Architecture La Salle,

Ramon Llull University (2002).

3D Studio MAX v.4 3D Studio MAX Course at the School of Architecture La Salle (2002).

Other: Windows environment, Internet Explorer, Microsoft Office Package,

Presto, Cypecad, 3D Studio Max v.6 (Course at the School of Architecture La Salle, Ramon Llull University, 2002 and Ases Academy Course, 2004).

Dear Sir/Madam,

I would like to present my CV as I am interested in joining your company.

I am located in Abu Dhabi looking for employment, at this moment, and I would be very grateful if you could receive me for an interview. **Mobile phone (24h): +971 52 675 9852**

I am an **Architect/Project Manager** with a degree in Architecture and 10 years experience in Construction, Design execution, Constructability and Project Management.

For the last few years I have fully engaged with site activities, supporting and assisting field engineers, managing site changes, monitoring progress and the execution of works and building small projects on my own.

In addition, I have recently finished a **MASTERS DEGREE COURSE in Project Management** at the Business Engineering School of La Salle, in Spain.

This gave me extremely valuable knowledge of Project Management and helped me to learn the skills and the technologies to properly manage any project.

My main interest in the field of **Project Management** is in the **Building and Civil Engineering** Sector, covering cost effectiveness, time, quality control, and all the skills required for new construction projects.

I am a confident person with good communication skills, a flexible professional profile, and I learn very quickly. I work very well under pressure, adapt myself to any work environment and have excellent planning and organizational capabilities. I believe team work is the best way to success and I am always motivated to take on new professional opportunities with initiative and enthusiasm.

I would like to thank you in advance for considering this application and I am willing to attend an interview at your convenience to explain any further details you may need. If necessary, I would be very happy to relocate at short notice and to travel.

I am looking forward to any feedback you may be able to give me.

Yours faithfully,

Myriam Cisteré

Email: myriamcistere@hotmail.com

Mobile phone Spain (24h): (+34) 657609032 Mobile phone EAU (24h): +971 52 675 9852

Skype: myriamcistere